Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
♪I've been searching for the past♪
♪لقد كنت أبحث عن الماضي♪
♪This world and the face that looks like yours♪
♪هذا العالم والوجه الذي يشبه وجهك♪
♪When I start to write♪
♪عندما أبدأ الكتابة♪
♪I realize I'm slowly walking into danger♪
♪أدرك أنني أسير ببطء نحو الخطر♪
♪I thought it was destined loneliness♪
♪اعتقدت أنها كانت الوحدة المقدرة♪
♪Through lifetimes of pain, the memory stays clear♪
♪على مر العصور من الألم، تبقى الذكرى واضحة♪
♪You again and again, me step by step♪
♪أنت مرارا وتكرارا، وأنا خطوة بخطوة♪
♪Lost on the road searching for you♪
♪ضائع على الطريق أبحث عنك♪
=A Fleeting Dream=
=حلم عابر=
=Episode 5=
=الحلقة 5=
Why are you home so late tonight?
لماذا عدت إلى المنزل متأخرًا هذه الليلة؟
I was talking with the Lian family's steward.
كنت أتحدث مع وكيل عائلة ليان.
Then, I ran into Lian Xinya, who caused some trouble.
ثم، التقيت بـ ليان شينيا، التي تسببت في بعض المشاكل.
You've been too close with that family's associates.
لقد كنت قريبًا جدًا من أفراد تلك العائلة.
Too many want to come after you.
هناك الكثير ممن يريدون المجيء إليك.
You need to be careful.
يجب عليك أن تكون حذرا.
With my skills,
مع مهاراتي،
you don't need to worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
But you've been back for quite some time now.
لكنك عدت منذ فترة طويلة الآن.
How's the matter with Pei Yujie?
كيف حال باي يوجي؟
Any progress?
أي تقدم؟
He is keeping too close of a watch on me.
إنه يراقبني عن كثب .
If I want to bring him down, I need more time.
إذا أردت إسقاطه، فأنا بحاجة إلى مزيد من الوقت.
You met with Jiang Yao.
لقد التقيت مع جيانج ياو.
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
I smelled the cologne he always uses.
لقد استنشقت رائحة الكولونيا التي يستخدمها دائمًا.
What are you? A hound?
ماذا أنت؟ كلب؟
You're my fiancée in name.
أنت خطيبتي بالإسم.
If you meet my niece's fiancé in private
إذا التقيت بخطيب ابنة أختي على انفراد
and someone sees it, we'll have unnecessary trouble.
وإذا رأى أحد ذلك، فسوف نواجه مشاكل لا داعي لها.
Unnecessary
غير ضروري
trouble?
مشكلة؟
Pei Yuze.
باي يوزي.
Don't tell me you...
لا تخبرني أنك...
I'm not.
انا لست كذلك.
Uncle, why are you in the mood to play chess with me today?
عمي، لماذا أنت في مزاج للعب الشطرنج معي اليوم؟
A game of chess shows a man's nature.
إن لعبة الشطرنج تظهر طبيعة الرجل.
Yao.
لهم.
If you only attack head-on
إذا هاجمت وجهاً لوجه فقط
and never look back,
ولا تنظر للخلف ابدًا
you may walk into danger without ever knowing it.
قد تدخل في خطر دون أن تعرف ذلك على الإطلاق.
Uncle, you're warning me with riddles.
عمي، أنت تحذرني بالألغاز.
Do you think we have some misunderstanding?
هل تعتقد أن لدينا بعض سوء الفهم؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Perfume I brought back from abroad.
العطر الذي أحضرته من الخارج.
It's light and fresh.
إنه خفيف و منعش.
You're still a Pei.
أنت لا تزال باي.
When you go out, don't let the family lose face.
عندما تخرج، لا تدع عائلتك تفقد ماء وجهها.
Bad news!
اخبار سيئة!
Mr. Jiang, Second Master.
السيد جيانج، المعلم الثاني.
News just came from the Lian family.
أخبار وصلت للتو من عائلة ليان.
They said Miss Xinruo's body has been found.
قالوا أنه تم العثور على جثة الآنسة شينرو.
Du Youmeng?
دو يومينج؟
Liar! How dare you come here?
كاذب! كيف تجرؤ على المجيء إلى هنا؟
Who is in this coffin?
من في هذا التابوت؟
My cousin, of course.
ابن عمي بالطبع.
Lian Xinruo.
ليان شينرو.
My dear cousin, are you sure?
ابن عمي العزيز هل أنت متأكد؟
I'm right here.
انا هنا .
How could I be mistaken?
كيف يمكن أن أكون مخطئا؟
The fishermen pulled the remains from the river.
قام الصيادون بسحب البقايا من النهر.
The clothes on the body
الملابس على الجسم
and the bracelet on the wrist prove it was Lian Xinruo.
والسوار الموجود على المعصم يثبت أنها ليان شينرو.
It's just a pile of bones.
إنها مجرد كومة من العظام.
If it wore your clothes
إذا ارتدت ملابسك
and your jewelry,
ومجوهراتك
then it could be Lian Xinya too!
إذن من الممكن أن تكون ليان شينيا أيضًا!
You...
أنت...
Du Youmeng.
دو يومينج.
You really do have a sharp tongue.
لديك لسان حاد حقا.
But the police already did an autopsy on the body.
لكن الشرطة قامت بالفعل بتشريح الجثة.
There is no doubt it was Lian Xinruo.
ليس هناك شك في أنها كانت ليان شينرو.
Or do you, Miss Du,
أم أنك، يا آنسة دو،
believe you're better at solving cases than the police?
هل تعتقد أنك أفضل من الشرطة في حل القضايا؟
Uncle Pei is absolutely right.
العم باي على حق تماما.
Du Youmeng, you pretended to be my cousin
دو يومينغ، لقد تظاهرت بأنك ابن عمي
and now you want to seize the Lian family's fortune.
والآن تريد الاستيلاء على ثروة عائلة ليان.
I'll have you taken
سأأخذك
to the police station for a hard lesson!
إلى مركز الشرطة لتلقي درس قاسٍ!
We'll see if you dare keep lying.
دعونا نرى إذا كنت تجرؤ على الاستمرار في الكذب.
That's right, you fraud.
هذا صحيح أيها المحتال.
How dare you pretend to be Miss Xinruo?
كيف تجرؤ على التظاهر بأنك الآنسة شينرو؟
Yes, send her to the police.
نعم، أرسلها إلى الشرطة.
See if she can lie again!
انظر هل تستطيع الكذب مرة أخرى!
Exactly.
بالضبط.
I didn't lie.
لم أكذب.
Wait.
انتظر.
What a lively scene.
ما أجمل هذا المشهد الحيوي!
I came just in time.
لقد جئت في الوقت المناسب.
Second Brother, your timing is perfect.
أخي الثاني توقيتك مثالي.
Du Youmeng is trying to commit fraud.
يحاول دو يومينغ ارتكاب عملية احتيال.
Xinya, as the victim, wants to send her to the police.
شينيا، باعتبارها الضحية، تريد إرسالها إلى الشرطة.
You're her husband.
أنت زوجها.
Go with her.
اذهب معها.
Brother.
أخ.
Isn't it a little too soon to jump to conclusions?
أليس من المبكر جدًا التوصل إلى استنتاجات؟
Pei Yuze, what are you doing?
بي يوزي، ماذا تفعل؟
Allow me to introduce him.
اسمحوا لي أن أقدمه لكم.
This is my friend from abroad, a forensic expert.
هذا صديقي من الخارج، خبير في الطب الشرعي.
He is an authority in the field.
فهو من ذوي السلطة في هذا المجال.
Since you can't agree,
بما أنك لا تستطيع الموافقة،
why don't we all take a look together
لماذا لا ننظر جميعا معا
and see if these remains really belong to Lian Xinruo.
وانظروا هل هذه البقايا تعود حقا إلى ليان شينرو.
That coroner works for you.
هذا الطبيب الشرعي يعمل لصالحك.
Of course he'll say whatever you want.
بالطبع سيقول كل ما تريد.
Whether it's true or not,
سواء كان ذلك صحيحا أم لا،
you can always check for yourself.
يمكنك دائمًا التحقق بنفسك.
The victim suffered blunt force trauma to the head.
تعرض الضحية لصدمة قوية في الرأس.
The victim did not die from drowning.
الضحية لم يمت غرقاً.
The remains are indeed of a girl about eighteen years old.
البقايا تعود بالفعل لفتاة تبلغ من العمر حوالي ثمانية عشر عامًا.
We also found soil in the sternum.
كما وجدنا أيضًا تربة في القص.
Through testing,
من خلال الاختبار،
we can confirm
يمكننا التأكيد
the body was not in water for long.
لم يبقى الجثمان في الماء لفترة طويلة.
It had been buried in the ground.
لقد تم دفنه في الأرض.
And the head had suffered severe trauma.
وكان الرأس قد تعرض لصدمة شديدة.
From this, we can conclude
ومن هذا يمكننا أن نستنتج
the girl did not die from drowning.
الفتاة لم تمت غرقا.
Lian Xinya.
ليان شينيا.
You tried to fool everyone with a body
لقد حاولت خداع الجميع بالجسد
dug from the ground.
حفرت من الأرض.
Do you think the rest of us are as stupid as you?
هل تعتقد أن بقيتنا أغبياء مثلك؟
You...
أنت...
A bunch of fools.
مجموعة من الحمقى.
- Let's go. - Let's leave.
- دعنا نذهب. - دعنا نغادر.
Yao, I need to go see Boss Lian.
ياو، أريد أن أذهب لرؤية الرئيس ليان.
Go home and take care of some work for me.
اذهب إلى المنزل وقم ببعض الأعمال من أجلي.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Pei Yuze, that friend of yours is amazing.
بي يوزي، صديقك هذا مذهل.
Where did you meet him?
أين التقيت به؟
His background is very mysterious. I can only tell you in secret.
خلفيته غامضة جدًا. لا أستطيع إخبارك إلا سرًا.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
He is an actor.
إنه ممثل.
That was too reckless!
لقد كان ذلك متهورًا جدًا!
What if they find out?
ماذا لو اكتشفوا ذلك؟
You're smart, and you didn't notice.
أنت ذكي ولم تلاحظ.
How would they?
كيف سيفعلون ذلك؟
Thank you, boss.
شكرا لك يا رئيس.
Remember to call me next time you have a job.
تذكر أن تتصل بي في المرة القادمة عندما يكون لديك عمل.
I just remembered
لقد تذكرت للتو
I have something to do.
عندي شيئا لأفعله.
Go back without me.
ارجع بدوني.
Who told you to act on your own?
من قال لك أن تتصرف بمفردك؟
Your sloppy little tricks ruined it!
حيلك الصغيرة السخيفة أفسدت الأمر!
Uncle Pei, I was wrong. It's all my fault.
عمي باي، كنتُ مخطئًا. كل هذا بسببي.
I was too impatient.
لقد كنت غير صبور للغاية.
I got careless.
لقد أصبحت مهملاً.
But now everyone in the Lian family
لكن الآن الجميع في عائلة ليان
is deceived by Du Youmeng.
تم خداعه من قبل دو يومينج.
Nobody believes me.
لا أحد يصدقني.
If this keeps up,
إذا استمر هذا،
I'll lose my place as head of the family.
سأفقد مكاني كرئيس للعائلة.
You've acted without my permission again and again.
لقد تصرفت دون إذني مرارا وتكرارا.
Do my words mean nothing to you?
هل كلامي لا يعني لك شيئا؟
Maybe I should find someone obedient to lead the Lian family.
ربما يجب علي أن أجد شخصًا مطيعًا لقيادة عائلة ليان.
No, please.
لا من فضلك.
Uncle Pei, I was wrong.
عمي باي، لقد كنت مخطئا.
I'm really sorry.
انا آسف حقا.
So now, does that mean there is nothing else we can do?
فهل يعني هذا الآن أنه لا يوجد شيء آخر يمكننا فعله؟
That is not for you to worry about.
هذا ليس من شأنك أن تقلق بشأنه.
I have my own plans.
لدي خططي الخاصة.
Brother, I'm here.
أخي أنا هنا.
(Shunyu Tailor Shop)
(متجر شونيو للخياطة)
Sorry, miss.
عذرا سيدتي.
An investigation is ongoing. Please leave.
التحقيق جارٍ. يُرجى المغادرة.
(Police Sergeant)
(رقيب شرطة)
Du Youmeng.
دو يومينج.
What are you really after?
ماذا تريد حقا؟
Uncle, your medicine is ready.
عمي، دوائك جاهز.
Uncle.
عم.
St. Mary's Hospital.
مستشفى سانت ماري.
Second Master.
المعلم الثاني.
Second Master!
المعلم الثاني!
Bad news, Second Master. Bad news!
أخبار سيئة يا سيدي الثاني. أخبار سيئة!
Mr. Jiang, why are you here?
السيد جيانج، لماذا أنت هنا؟
Me? I came to deliver medicine to Uncle.
أنا؟ جئت لأوصل الدواء إلى عمي.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
On her way back, Miss was caught in a gang shootout.
في طريق عودتها، تعرضت السيدة لإطلاق نار من قبل عصابة.
We don't know if she's alive or dead.
نحن لا نعلم إذا كانت حية أم ميتة.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
Perhaps the job is done?
ربما تم الانتهاء من المهمة؟
♪The city night silently envelops♪
♪ليلة المدينة تغلف بصمت♪
♪Hate and love♪
♪الكراهية والحب♪
♪His voice lingers by my ear♪
♪صوته يبقى في أذني♪
♪In this unavoidable dead end I encounter♪
♪في هذا الطريق المسدود الذي لا مفر منه الذي أواجهه♪
♪How can wounded love burn again♪
♪كيف يمكن للحب الجريح أن يحترق مرة أخرى♪
♪Leaving only his unpredictable smile♪
♪لم يبق منه سوى ابتسامته غير المتوقعة♪
♪My heart receives his gentle signals drop by drop♪
♪يستقبل قلبي إشاراته اللطيفة قطرة قطرة♪
♪Wounded wings try to rely on♪
♪الأجنحة الجريحة تحاول الاعتماد على♪
♪Secret love♪
♪الحب السري♪
♪Hidden in his most passionate embrace♪
♪مختبئ في أحضانه الأكثر شغفًا♪
♪Ignoring the noisy lights and wine♪
♪ تجاهل الأضواء الصاخبة والنبيذ ♪
♪Being a quiet cat in his arms♪
♪أكون قطة هادئة بين ذراعيه♪
♪Entwining the rest of my life, with no escape♪
♪تشابك بقية حياتي، بلا مفر♪